# Vedran Arnautovic

Senior UX Designer

527 Brunswick Street Fitzroy North VIC 3068

phone 0434 490 076 web vedran.io email hello@vedran.io twitter @vedranio

I'm a user centred designer with over 10 years' experience, focusing on UX design, usability, interaction design and user research.

I'm interested in development of design teams through mentoring and integration of modern design tools and practices into their workflows.

# Experience

#### **SEEK**

Jan 2014 - present

## Senior UX Designer

I've led design on key initiatives within SEEK's advertiser portfolio, often crossing over both sides of the marketplace.

My work is a mixture of tactical projects where I closely work with small agile teams, and more strategic efforts where I've worked with senior leaders to define the future of SEEK's products.

// Keywords

UX, UI, workshop facilitation, user research, usability testing, prototyping, agile, lean UX

#### **Freelance**

Sep 2016 – present

#### Freelance UX designer

#### **Gymsales**

I lead design for Gymsales, working closely with the CEO and the dev team.

// Keywords

UI, information architecture, iPad, animation design

#### Rubicon

I ran a design sprint for Rubicon's Dutch clients and developed a prototype for the solution we came up with during the sprint.

// Keywords google design sprint, workshop facilitation, wireframe, prototype, coaching, mentoring

#### **Kolektiv**

Over a period of 6 months, I coached Kolektiv's product team on usability testing and lean UX practices.

// Keywords usability testing, lean UX, coaching, mentoring

#### **SMS**

Sep 2010 - Jan 2014

## Consultant (UX designer and BA)

During my time at SMS, I worked for three clients

- UX Designer and BA (NAB)
- UX Designer (NAB)
- Interface Designer and BA (BP)

Internally, I was appointed the Customer Experience (CX) lead for Victoria kickstarted the development of our CX capability.

// Keywords
Usability testing, UI design, workshop facilitation, journey mapping, interface design

#### Leica

Feb 2009 - Sep 2010 Melbourne

#### System Design Engineer & BA

Upon returning to Melbourne, I worked with Leica's software team and got an opportunity to define a number of design improvements based on my research in the field.

// Keywords
UI design, wireframes, system design, business analysis

#### Leica

Feb 2007 - Feb 2009 London

### **System Design Engineer**

A career shaping opportunity allowed me to spend two years researching how our clients and support teams interacted with our instruments, and to use those findings to design better solutions for them.

// Keywords user research, contextual enquiry, process design, system design

## **Vision BioSystems**

Jan 2004 - Feb 2007

#### **Software Engineer**

I started out very technical, developing software for medical devices. Working in an organisation with no designers created a window of opportunity to start designing and show initiative to test software with users.

// Keywords software developer, UI design, user testing

# Education

#### Univ. of Melbourne

1999 - 2004

Bachelor's degree, Computer Science

Bachelor's degree, Mechatronics

# Tools

Sketch, Adobe CC, Marvel, Invision, Axure, Morae, Principle, Framer.js, CSS, HTML, Javascript, Github

+ anything else I need to learn.